secureaplus.com 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy | SecureAPlus

## III. Protection of Collected Information

SecureAge Technology complies with the Personal Data Protection Act in Singapore and the international information security standards in order to protect your personal data. This ensures that your personal data is protected from abuse, unauthorized access and disclosure, damage, manipulation or deleting. As long as it is within SecureAge site, your personal information is transmitted encrypted via SSL (Secure Socket Layer) protocol.

You have the right to access your personal data, the right to correct such data, the right to request explanations regarding processing of your personal data and to require remedies such as blocking, correction, supplementing or liquidation of personal data if the processing is contrary to protection of your private and personal life or in contradiction with law.

SecureAge Technology takes measures to ensure that any collected information will receive an adequate level of protection if and when transferred. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy or any Documentation or other materials provided to you in connection with the SecureAPlus software, SecureAge Technology reserves all rights to cooperate with any legal process or government inquiry (including, but not limited to, court orders and law enforcement requests) related to your use of the SecureAPlus software. In connection with such cooperation, SecureAge Technology may provide documents and information relevant to a court subpoena or government or other legal investigation, which may include disclosure of your personally identifiable information. SecureAge Technology may also use statistics derived from the collected information to track and publish reports on security risk trends.

By using the SecureAPlus software, you acknowledge and agree that SecureAge Technology may collect, transmit, store, disclose and analyze such information for any of the foregoing purposes listed in this Section.
